{
    "id": "877c9e9543cf45e6ac09395fc2a72888",
    "title": "Other And Another",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has bought ………………. car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "an other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1ca7b8ad22904e4d86a5b1a5bad12fa5"
        },
        {
            "question": "They looked into each ………………… eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "others",
                "other's",
                "another's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da33c1851dd34c858a138c33f7d23750"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could I have ………………. cup of coffee, please?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "an other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75736792db714a7f981713b949a7e92d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We all should love one ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "an other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f30774d8fa5544e88a276e82e5e796be"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………… people haven’t arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "an other"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c659b0f67dc246b1a7ea07878de6ae69"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many ……………….. feel the same.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1378736f36a046669df1a7b5abaa72f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ve met James, but I haven’t met the ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4ab10cdfc1f4e8ca0de80eb354068b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is staying here for ………………. few weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a968f3c94b464d018d657cd1d4d45ee3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don’t you think about …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "814d6c78efb4407ba7cf52836c4b28d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are the …………….. photos?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b9a63e59a254f3c8a67a8b4e12b0795"
        }
    ]
}